Finding Aid for the Tom Schulman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Tom Schulman Papers
1942-2005
University Archives
MSS.0936
13.75 linear_feet
- Scripts
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 7/4/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 7/10/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 8/2/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/1/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/29/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 12/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 1/23/91 (Box 1)
  - “Treeman” (aka Medicine Man) (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 8/2/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 8/2/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) draft – 8/2/90 (Box 1)
  - Medicine Man Script Fragments Folder 2 – 8/2/90- 9/24/90 (Box 1)
  - Eden or The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 9/21/90 (Box 1)
  - Eden or The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 9/21/90 (Box 1)
  - The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 9/26/90 (Box 1)
  - The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 9/26/90 (Box 1)
  - The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 9/29/90 (Box 1)
  - The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/1/90 (Box 1)
  - The Last Eden (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/1/90 (Box 1)
  - Medicine Man Script Fragments Folder 2 – 10/17/90 – 10/18/90 (Box 1)
  - Medicine Man Script Fragments Folder 3 – 10/18/90 – 10/23/90 (Box 1)
  - Medicine Man Script Fragments Folder 4 – 10/24/90 – 10/28/90 (Box 1)
  - The Cure (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/29/90 (Box 1)
  - The Cure (aka Medicine Man) draft – 10/29/90 (Box 1)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script fragments and notes 1- 1990 October 31- 1990 December 18 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script fragments and notes 2- 1991 January 17- 1991 January 24 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script revised first draft numbered 003473- 1990 October 29 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 003664- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 003776- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 003888- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004001- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004221- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004111- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004311- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004441- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (multi titled draft) script numbered 004551- 1991 January 21 (Box 2)
  - Campbell’s Stand (aka Medicine Man) script- 1991 January 23 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script fragments, research, notes- 1990 June 20 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script- 1990 August 2 (Box 2)
  - The Stand (aka Medicine Man) script- 1990 August 2 (Box 2)
  - Treeman (first draft of Medicine Man/The Stand) script- 1990 February 5 (Box 2)
  - WAB – 1990 September 8 (Box 2)
  - WAB – 1990 September 10 (Box 2)
  - WAB – 1990 September 13 (Box 2)
  - WAB – Final Version – 1990 September 17 (Box 2)
  - WAB – Notes from Disney (Box 2)
  - WAB – Television Personalities “Bob” Versions (Box 2)
  - Dancing Man script (First Draft)- No Date (Box 2)
  - Dancing Man script- 1991 November 13 (Box 2)
  - Dancing Man script with various notes- 1991 August 20 (Box 2)
  - Dancing Man script fragments and notes- No Date (Box 2)
  - Dancing Man script- 1991 October 18 (Box 2)
  - WAB – 1988 August 26 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 August 30 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 September 1 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 October 20 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 October 26 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 October 27 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 October 28 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 November 17 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1988 December 1 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1989 March 7 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1989 March 31 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1989 April 14 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 May 12 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 May 14 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 May 15 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 June (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 July 14 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 July 26 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 August 13 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 August 15 (Box 3)
  - WAB – 1990 September 6 (Box 3)
  - Dancing Man script fragments and general notes (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script Fragments and general notes 2 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1991 October 18 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- First Draft (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1991 October 13 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1991 October 26 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1992 February 18 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1992 February 16 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Second Draft)- 1992 February 13 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Second Draft)- 1992 February 28 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Second Draft)- 1992 February 29 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Second Draft)- 1992 February 18 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Revised Second Draft)- 1992 February 23 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Revised Second Draft)- 1992 February 23 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Revised Second Draft)- 1992 March 20 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Revised Second Draft)- 1992 March 19 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Revised Second Draft)- 1992 March 18 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script (Second Draft)- 1992 March 12 (Box 4)
  - The Soldier of the Realm (AKA The Dancing Man)- No Date (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 May 20 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 May 19 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 April 20 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 March 18 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- (No cover)- No Date (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 May 6 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 May 6 (Box 4)
  - Dancing Man script- 1994 May 6 (Box 4)
  - Holy Man script fragment (Temp 1) (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (45a) (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (Notes for 45)- 1994 January 19 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man misc. script notes- 1993 December (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (29)- No Date (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (28, Miriam’s Notes)- No Date (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 September 17 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 September 17 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (21)- 1993 August 30 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (22)- 1993 August 30 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (23) – No Date (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (24) – No Date (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 August 13 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man misc. script fragments folder 1 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man misc. script fragments folder 2 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man misc. script fragments folder 3 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script edit slips (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1994 January 19 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1994 May 1 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script (Revised Second Draft)- No Date (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1995 January 17 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1995 January 13 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1994 May 1 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1994 May 1 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man misc. script notes 1994-1995 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1994 January 19 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 November 5 (Box 5)
  - Holy Man script- 1995 February 28 (Box 6)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 November 5 (Box 6)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 October 8 (Box 6)
  - Holy Man script- 1993 September 17 (Box 6)
  - Holy Man script (First Draft)- 1993 August 13 (Box 6)
  - Holy Man administrative file (budget, costume design, D.P.S, editors, schedules, make-up artists) (Box 6)
  - The Answer script (Registered WGAw)- No Date (Box 6)
  - The Answer script (Edited; includes Editing slips) (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script- 1995 March 19 (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script- No Date (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script- 1995 March 10 (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script (heavily edited)- No Date (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script (3rd Draft)- 1994 October 13 (Box 6)
  - Down Periscope script (1st Draft)- 1995 February 9 (Box 6)
  - Baal script- 1994 December 13 (Box 6)
  - Baal script- 1997 October 1 (Box 6)
  - Baal script (labeled Baal 1)- No Date (Box 6)
  - Baal script (labeled Baal 2)- No Date (Box 6)
  - Baal script- 1997 October 3 (Box 6)
  - Casablanca script- 1942 June 1 (Box 7)
  - Rent-A-Cops script (1st Draft)- No Date (Box 7)
  - Protect and Serve (aka Rent-A-Cops) script- No Date (Box 7)
  - The Court script- 1998 December 17 (Box 7)
  - The Flame script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Misc. script Fragments (Box 7)
  - Righteous Fury script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Protect and Serve (aka Rent-A-Cops) script-1985 October 24 (Box 7)
  - The Case of Leo Frank script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Reliable General script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Sarcophagus script- 1977 (Box 7)
  - Hot Water script- 1987 October 1 (Box 7)
  - Hot Water script-1987 October 16 (Box 7)
  - Komodo Ken script (with edits)- No Date (Box 7)
  - Shooting Star script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Louis and Clarke script- 1991 April 17 (Box 7)
  - Tell Me True script- 1990 March 4 (Box 7)
  - Wolfbeiner script- 1987 February 27 (Box 7)
  - Big Man on Campus script- 1992 October 23 (Box 7)
  - Big Man on Campus (or Campus King/King of the Campus) script/plot summary (Box 7)
  - The Gladiator script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Score: A Situation Comedy script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Genius Willie Parker script- 1974 September 27 (Box 7)
  - Reliable General script- No Date (Box 7)
  - The Case of Leo Frank script- No Date (Box 7)
  - The Warp script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Sarcophagus script- 1977 (Box 7)
  - Prosperity: A Comedy script- No Date (Box 7)
  - Rampage script- No Date (Box 7)
  - The Fifth Commandment script – 1990 March 20 (Box 8)
  - King Iz script – 1990 March 20 (Box 8)
  - The Warrior Monk script and research – Circa 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Great Bandini script and research- 1991 (Box 8)
  - Alien Zoo concept art, summaries, and script (Box 8)
  - New America script and research- Circa 1991 (Box 8)
  - Mondo Jocko script- No Date (Box 8)
  - Mondo Jocko script- No Date (Box 8)
  - The Fool script- 1995 April 1 (Box 8)
  - Armed and Dangerous script- No Date (Box 8)
  - Golden Years script- 1990 March 20 (Box 8)
  - Golden Years script- 1990 April 26 (Box 8)
  - Diaspora script- 1991 September 12 (Box 8)
  - Daily Reminders and schedules- 1991 September 12 (Box 8)
  - Theme and Variations script- 1996 January 28 (Box 8)
  - Untitled script about sports- No Date (Box 8)
  - Script titled “I.P. Tom’s Rewrite”- No Date (Box 8)
  - First Knight script- 1994 June 17 (Box 8)
  - First Knight script (Tom Schulman Rewrite)- 1993 February 6 (Box 8)
  - The Goddess script- No Date (Box 8)
  - Price script- No Date (Box 8)
  - Price script (23rd Draft)- No Date (Box 8)
  - Price script- No Date (Box 8)
  - DPS – Shooting Schedule – 1988 November 3 (Box 9)
  - DPS – Final Shooting Draft – 1988 December 20 (Box 9)
  - DPS – Third Draft – 1988 August 28 (Box 9)
  - DPS – Revised Third Draft – 1988 September 29 (Box 9)
  - DPS – Revised Third Draft – 1988 December 20 (Box 9)
  - DPS – Revised Second Draft – 1987 October 7 (Box 9)
  - DPS – unlabeled drafts x8 (Box 9)
  - The Tennie Weenies (aka Honey, I Shrunk the Kids) script- 1987 March 27 (Box 9)
  - Grounded (aka Honey, I Shrunk the Kids) script- 1988 January 28 (Box 9)
  - Honey, I Shrunk the Kids Drawings (Box 9)
  - Love at Second Sight script- No Date (Box 9)
  - Second Sight script- 1987 December 7 (Box 9)
  - Love at Second Sight script (2nd Draft)- 1987 May 5 (Box 9)
  - Love at Second Sight script (2nd Draft Revised)- 1987 July 16 (Box 9)
  - Love at Second Sight script- No Date (Box 9)
  - Frank script- 1994 March 14 (Box 9)
  - Frank script (First Draft Revised)- 1992 October 15 (Box 9)
  - Frank script- 1994 March 14 (Box 10)
  - Frank script- 1995 April 5 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script- 1999 February 18 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport note cards- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport outline notes- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 9)- 1998 August 19 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport (aka Mr. President)- 1998 September 25 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 20)- 1998 October 23 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 21, 1 of 2)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 21, 2 of 2)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 22)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 23)- 1998 November 11 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 24)- 1998 December 10 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script (Draft 32)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport materials (promo materials, premiere invitations, film events, crew directory, contracts, and articles- 2003-2004 (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script- 2003 April-July (Box 10)
  - Welcome to Mooseport script- 2003 May 23 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 April 13 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 April 19 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 8)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 May 2 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 May 4 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script fragment (1st Version)- 1995 May 5 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 12)- No Date (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 13)- 1995 July 5 (Box 10)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 14)- No Date (Box 11)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 20)- 1996 May 8 (Box 11)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script (Draft 21)- 1996 May 16 (Box 11)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 April 21 (Box 11)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1995 May 4 (Box 11)
  - Eight Heads in a Duffle Bag script- 1996 July 3 (Box 11)
  - Walk of Fame script (Revised by Schulman)- 2000 March 21 (Box 11)
  - Burn Baby Burn script (numbered 028838)- No Date (Box 11)
  - Walk of Fame script (based on Burn Baby Burn)- 1998 July 30 (Box 11)
  - The Inheritance/Grandparents Discord script with edit slips- No Date (Box 11)
  - The Inheritance/Grandparents Discord script with edit slips 2- No Date (Box 11)
  - The Inheritance/Grandparents Discord folder with script notes, edit slips, script fragments. (Box 11)
  - Millennium Scavenger Hunt notes, research, info- 1999 (Box 11)
  - New World Order research- 1997 (Box 11)
  - Noel Evans Case Research- 2002 (Box 11)
  - Filmographies and Writers Guild of America Screenplay Registrations- 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Folder of Cast Ideas- No Date (Box 11)
  - Call Sheets 1- 1993 September 17- 1994 March 9 (Box 11)
  - Call Sheets 2- 1993 September 29-1995 May 2 (Box 11)
  - Call Sheets 3- 1994 March 10- 1994 September 27 (Box 11)